shefinds.com 2018-10-09

# Privacy Policy

This policy was last updated April 2015.

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy describes the information we gather, how we share that  
information and what we do to protect your information.

Personal Information  
SHEfinds requires your e-mail address when you subscribe to our newsletters, when you sign up for sweepstakes, and when you take advantage of other services our website offers. To provide you with the best possible service, we also require some basic personal information when you sign up. Those items are marked with an asterisk (*). Furthermore, we ask for some optional information on our sign-up page and in periodic opt-in surveys. We use this basic and optional information, to further tailor our content to your interests. Upon request, we will provide you with the information that we maintain about you.

Demographic Information  
We may use aggregate data such as income, age and geography to further customize our content and enhance our  
services. We may share this information with advertisers and the media. Likewise, we may share this information with another company in the event that we merge, are acquired or participate in a joint venture with another company, or if we conclude that we are required by law to share it. All aggregate data will be shared without any personally identifiable  
information about our individual subscribers.

Cookies  
We and some of our partners may make use of cookies (small text files placed on your computer’s hard disk by our server). They are used to collect traffic information such as the number of visits to our site and pages visited. This  
information will be used to assess how visitors are using our services. This data will also allow us to manage the functionality of the site. You can disable cookies at any time if your browser permits.

Web Site Usage Information  
We and our partners also may make use of pixel tags which also collect traffic information regarding the behavior and usage patterns of users of our site. Pixel tags allow us, or a third party who provides the pixel tag, to set, read, and modify cookies on, and to transfer other data to, the browser used to view the Web page or other document. Pixel tags may also be used to obtain information about the computer being used to view that Web page or other document, including the sites the users of that computer visit.. The entity that provides the tag can view the IP address of the computer that the tag is sent to, the time it was sent, the user’s operating system and browser type, and similar information. Our partners may use this information to display advertisements and other content that targeted to you. We may also use other  
technologies that permit data gathering.

You may chose not to accept a pixel tag by taking one of the following three actions:

First, you can opt-out using our partner Blue Kai’s opt-out process, which is explained here http://www.bluekai.com/optout.html.

Second, you can also opt-out by using the NAI’s opt-out tool, which is explained here http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp

These two options require you to accept cookies, and they will only function if your browser is set to accept third-party cookies. If you delete an opt-out cookie from a browser’s cookie files, the pixel tag will be installed until an opt-out cookie is reset on that browser.

The third way to block pixel tags is to block third-party cookies on your browser. If you block third-party cookies from being set on your browser, you may not be able to enjoy some features or functionality of, and you may see the same content and advertisements repeatedly on, some Web sites.

Linked Sites  
Although SHEfinds may provide links to third party sites, and advertisements from third parties, we are not responsible for the content that appears on those sites nor do we endorse these sites. Please review each site’s privacy policy to  
determine their use of information.

Advertisers  
To support our efforts we sell sponsorships of SHEfinds mailings and on the blog to advertisers who we think you’d like to know about. Collection, use, disclosure and security of information collected by advertisers are subject to the privacy policies of those advertisers.

Agents  
From time to time, we may use the services of third-party companies to help facilitate our business activities. These include affiliate or incentive program providers, customer service organizations, e-mail and postal mail brokers, and marketing service providers. These companies are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and are prohibited from using the information we provide for any reason except to perform the functions that we have outlined for them.

Opt-out / Unsubscribe  
If we ever send you an email that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request to receive no future notices.

Changes to Privacy Policy  
SHEfinds may change this privacy policy. Any changes will be reflected on this privacy policy page. If you are concerned about how your information will be used, you should check back at this privacy policy page periodically.

Children  
We do not intentionally collect any information from children.

Contact  
If you should have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

This policy was last updated April 2015.

White Cat Media, Inc.  
121 West 27th Street  
Suite 701  
New York, NY 10001
